[Music]
[音乐]
hi my name is Chris Haggerty I work in
嗨，我叫克里斯·哈格蒂（Chris Haggerty），我在这里工作
the Java platform group at Oracle and
Oracle的Java平台小组和
today I'm going to be talking about
今天我要说的是
handling response data with the Java 11
使用Java 11处理响应数据
HTTP client in this session we're going
在此会话中的HTTP客户端
to take a high-level look at three
从高层次看三个
active streams interfaces in the Java
Java中的活动流接口
platform and how they operate using this
平台及其使用方式
knowledge we will then see how the HTTP
知识之后，我们将了解HTTP
client leverages these interfaces to
客户利用这些接口来
handle request and response bodies will
处理请求和响应机构
work through an example of how to write
通过一个如何写作的例子
a custom response body subscriber and
定制响应主体订户，以及
how to interoperate with existing flow
如何与现有流程互操作
publishers and subscribers before
之前的发布者和订阅者
looking at the reactive streams it is
看着反应流
useful to remind ourselves of the
有助于提醒自己
classic producer/consumer paradigm and
经典的生产者/消费者范例和
some of the potential concerns and
一些潜在的问题和
issues with it typically the producer
通常是生产者的问题
generates items or data puts them in a
生成项目或数据将其放入
queue or buffer of sorts at the same
相同的队列或缓冲区
time the consumer consumes the data by
消费者消耗数据的时间
removing items one at a time from the
一次从
buffer the problem was how to make sure
缓冲问题是如何确保
that the producer is not blocked when
当生产者没有被阻止时
the buffer becomes full or that the
缓冲区已满或
consumer is not trying to get data when
消费者在以下情况下不尝试获取数据
the buffer is empty and had a
缓冲区为空，并且有一个
notification mechanism to implement such
通知机制来实现
if it happens as well as trying to
如果发生以及尝试
determine a reasonable buffer size
确定合理的缓冲区大小
moving to reactive streams the producer
转向反应性生产者
is known as a publisher that publishes
被称为发布者
items the consumer is known as a
被消费者称为
subscriber that receives items the
接收项目的订户
publisher has a single method subscribed
发布者订阅了一个方法
that takes a subscriber the subscriber
需要一个订阅者
has four methods unsubscribe on next on
有四种取消订阅的方法
error and uncomplete we'll take a look
错误和不完整，我们来看一下
at these now subscriber can be
现在，这些用户可以是
subscribed to a publisher by calling the
通过调用
publisher subscribed method and passing
发布者订阅的方法和传递
the subscriber to publish our den calls
订户发布我们的电话
the subscribers unsubscribe method with
订户的退订方法
a subscription this handshake between
两次握手之间的订阅
the subscriber and the publisher results
订阅者和发布者结果
in the publisher having a reference to
在发布者中引用
the subscriber
订户
subscriber having the publisher
拥有发布者的订户
subscription that it was given in
所提供的订阅
unsubscribing it is the subscription
取消订阅是订阅
that acts as a mechanism for the
作为一种机制
subscriber to send signals to the
订户向
publisher for example using this
发布者例如使用此
subscription the subscriber can request
订阅者可以请求的订阅
a number of items from the publisher the
出版商的一些物品
publisher can then publish at most that
然后，发布者最多可以发布
number of items by calling the
通过调用
subscribers on next methods and number
订户了解下一种方法和编号
of times each with a single item this
每次都有一个项目的次数
request mechanism provides the
请求机制提供了
subscriber with back pressure since it
订户具有背压，因为它
is in control of the maximum number of
控制最大数量
items that may be sent to it if the
如果
publisher has no more items to publish
发布者没有其他要发布的项目
then it calls subscribers on complete
然后呼叫订户
method this informs the subscriber that
通知订户的方法
the publisher regardless of demand for
发行人，无论需求如何
more items will publish no more items to
更多项目将不会发布更多项目给
dis subscriber if the publisher
Dis订阅者（如果发布者）
encounters an error say reading from a
遇到错误，请说从
file or network then it informs the
文件或网络，然后通知
subscriber of this by calling the
的订户，请致电
subscribers on error method with a
订户使用错误方法
suitable trouble indicating the problem
适当的故障指示问题
the Java platform provides support for
Java平台提供了对
reactive streams to a number of
反应流到许多
interfaces in the java.util concurrent
java.util中的并发接口
flow class there is a publisher for
流类有一个发布者
publishing items a subscriber for
发布订户的项目
receiving items a subscriber subscribes
接收订户订阅的项目
to the publisher and can issue requests
给发布者，可以发出请求
for items as needed the HTTP client
用于HTTP客户端所需的项目
models request body using a subtype of
模型使用以下类型的子类型请求正文
flow publisher a request body publisher
流发布者请求主体发布者
the HTTP client subscribes to this
HTTP客户端订阅此
publisher when sending a request to has
发布商发送请求到
body on the receiving side when a
身体在接收方时
response code and headers are received
收到响应代码和标头
the HTTP client calls the body hunger
HTTP客户端称呼身体饥饿
the body hunger can then inspect these
人体饥饿可以检查这些
values if it wishes before creating a
如果愿意，可以在创建一个
body subscriber this subscriber returned
该订阅者返回的正文订阅者
by the body hunter will be used to
由身体猎人会习惯
receive and process the actual response
接收并处理实际响应
body bytes the HTTP body subscriber is a
正文字节，HTTP正文订阅者是
subtype of flow subscriber
流订阅者的子类型
and httpclient acts as a publisher of
并且httpclient充当以下内容的发布者：
response buddy bytes there are a number
响应伙伴字节中有一个数字
of factories for creating body
制造身体的工厂
publishers and body subscribers for most
大多数的出版商和团体订阅者
common use cases like publishing request
常见用例，例如发布请求
body from a string or from a file or
字符串或文件中的主体
converting response body bytes into a
将响应主体字节转换为
string or streaming them to a file in
字符串或将它们流式传输到文件中
this session we're going to focus on the
本届会议我们将重点关注
response body handler is a functional
响应主体处理程序具有功能
interface that has a single methods
具有单一方法的接口
apply that takes a response info
应用需要回复信息
containing the status code and headers
包含状态码和标题
the body handler is invoked when the
当
response status code and headers are
响应状态代码和标头为
available but before the actual response
可用，但在实际回复之前
body bytes have been received the body
正文字节已收到正文
handler can inspect the response code
处理程序可以检查响应代码
and headers before returning the body
和标题，然后再返回正文
subscriber the body subscriber will then
然后，主体订阅者将
be used to receive the actual response
用于接收实际的响应
body bytes body subscriber is a flow
主体字节主体订户是流
subscriber of an aggregate of byte
字节总数的订户
buffers the byte buffers contained
缓冲包含的字节缓冲区
response body bytes by the subscriber
订户的响应正文字节
has a single abstract method get' body
有一个抽象方法get'body
that returns a completion stage that
返回完成阶段
completes with a higher-level type that
用更高级别的类型完成
the body subscriber implementation will
主体订户实施将
convert the response body bytes into the
将响应主体字节转换为
body subscriber class contains only
主体订户类仅包含
study static factory methods and these
研究静态工厂方法以及这些
methods are factories for creating body
方法是制造身体的工厂
subscribers that can be used for most
可以用于大多数用户
common use cases by converting the
常见用例通过转换
response body into a byte array or
响应主体转换为字节数组或
string or streaming it to a file or an
字符串或将其流式传输到文件或
input stream let's take a look at
输入流让我们看一下
writing a custom body subscriber for
为...编写自定义主体订户
handling response data okay so let's
处理响应数据好吧，让我们
take a look at how to write a custom
看看如何编写自定义
body hunger and body subscriber before
身体饥饿和身体订户之前
doing that let's take a look at how one
这样做，让我们来看看如何
of the convenience body handlers works
便利车身搬运工的工作
so here we've got a utility get method
所以这里我们有一个实用的get方法
it retrieves a given URI and returns the
它检索给定的URI并返回
response body as a string so first it
响应主体为字符串，因此首先
creates a new HTTP client over which the
创建一个新的HTTP客户端，通过该客户端
request
请求
we sent and it builds a request from the
我们发送了，它从
given URI then it calls the send async
给定URI，然后调用发送异步
method to send a request that he uses
发送他使用的请求的方法
the body handlers of string static
静态字符串的主体处理程序
factory method to create a body handler
创建身体处理程序的工厂方法
that converts the response body bytes to
将响应主体字节转换为
a string then the completable future
一个字符串，然后是可完成的未来
then apply method maps the HTTP response
然后apply方法映射HTTP响应
of string to its body type in our cases
在我们的案例中，字符串与其主体类型有关
string and a completable future of
字符串和一个可完成的未来
string is returned so we can see example
返回字符串，所以我们可以看到示例
new switch of this get methods in the
get方法中的新开关
main method so here we can see the get
主要方法，所以在这里我们可以看到
method is being passed URI and then join
方法正在传递URI，然后加入
is being called on the computer for
在计算机上被称为
future that's returns this blocks
返回的未来
execution until the string response body
执行直到字符串响应主体
is available and then the program simply
是可用的，然后该程序只需
prints out the body so let's run that so
打印出身体，让我们运行
here we can see the response body string
在这里我们可以看到响应正文字符串
being printed out and it's just some XML
被打印出来，它只是一些XML
this point it'd be useful to see the
在这一点上，看到
response status code so let's print that
响应状态代码，让我们打印出来
so here we use in the completable future
所以在这里我们用在可完成的未来
when complete methods to print out the
当完整的方法打印出来
status code really we should be checking
状态码我们应该检查一下
that the response value is none no in
响应值为none no in
case an error happens for simplicity and
为了简单起见，发生错误
just print it for now so running that
暂时将其打印出来，这样运行
again okay great we can see the response
再次好吧，我们可以看到响应
code is 200 so everything is okay and
代码是200，所以一切正常
again the response body is printed all
再次将响应主体全部打印
right so that's everything working using
正确，这就是所有正在使用的东西
one of the convenience body handers
方便身体处理者之一
let's take a look at writing our own so
让我们来看看自己写的
we need to implement the body subscriber
我们需要实现主体订户
interface and in this case our type is a
接口，在这种情况下，我们的类型是
string okay so the body subscriber has a
字符串好，因此主体订阅者有一个
single method called get body and a
称为get body和a的单一方法
return to completion stage of T T is a
返回TT的完成阶段是
string in our case and we must also
在我们的情况下，我们还必须
implement the four methods from flow
从流程实现四种方法
subscriber so let's take a look at them
订阅者，让我们来看看他们
we'll start with the get body method so
我们将从get body方法开始
they get body method needs to return a
他们得到身体方法需要返回一个
completion stage of string so let's use
字符串的完成阶段，让我们使用
complete of a future which is a concrete
一个具体的未来的完成
implementation of a completion stage
完成阶段的实施
so which called our compatible teacher
所以叫我们兼容的老师
hey buddy cf because it holds the
嘿哥们CF，因为它拥有
response body and where you can return
响应主体以及可以返回的位置
that from the cat body method now I'll
从猫的身体方法，我现在
move on to unsubscribe so the HTTP
继续取消订阅，以便HTTP
clients is a publisher and response body
客户是发布者和响应机构
and this string subscriber subscribe to
这个字符串订阅者订阅
that publisher so first it will have its
该发行商，因此首先它将拥有其
unsubscribe method invoked with the
用调用的取消订阅方法
subscription from the HTTP client so
来自HTTP客户端的订阅，因此
let's store that subscription
让我们存储该订阅
okay now we have the subscription we can
好吧，现在我们可以订阅了
request some more response body from the
请求其他响应主体
client or we can cancel a subscription
客户，或者我们可以取消订阅
if we're no longer interested let's
如果我们不再感兴趣，让我们
request some more and just request one
要求更多，只要求一个
at this point we can look up hook up
在这一点上，我们可以查找挂钩
error handling so we complete the body
错误处理，所以我们完成了正文
cf exceptionally after an error happens
错误发生后异常
in this simplement implementation then
在这个简单的实现中
just accumulate all of response data on
只是积累所有的响应数据
the pipe buffers in the list and then we
列表中的管道缓冲区，然后我们
will convert the response body into a
会将响应主体转换为
string at the end so let's create a list
末尾的字符串，让我们创建一个列表
okay so every time response data is
好的，所以每次响应数据是
received we add it to the list
收到，我们将其添加到列表中
let's keep that a better name okay great
让我们保留一个更好的名字好吧
so we're only left with the uncomplete
所以我们只剩下不完整的
method so again in this simple move
方法如此简单
implementation we will just determine
实施，我们将确定
the number of bytes we have put them in
我们放入它们的字节数
a byte array and then convert that byte
字节数组，然后转换该字节
array into a string
排列成字符串
so once we know the number of bytes are
所以一旦我们知道字节数是
remaining in each byte buffer we can sum
每个字节缓冲区中剩余的空间我们可以求和
that up so that's the total number of
那就是总数
bytes that we need in our byte array so
我们字节数组中需要的字节
let's create a fight array of that size
让我们创建一个这样大小的战斗阵列
okay now we can iterate over the buffers
好吧，现在我们可以遍历缓冲区了
and that them to a byte array oops
并且它们到字节数组哎呀
call that buffers show people for over
呼叫缓冲区显示人员结束
doc gets byte array at this point we
doc此时获取字节数组，我们
need an offsets so it's great one so
需要补偿，所以很棒
there should be zero and we need a
应该为零，我们需要一个
length and the length is going to be the
长度，长度将是
number of bytes remaining
剩余字节数
and this is offset you will need to
这是抵消，您将需要
increase the offset as we iterate okay
随着我们迭代好，增加偏移量
now we have a response but he bytes in a
现在我们有一个回应，但他在
byte array let's convert that to a
字节数组让我们将其转换为
string for simplicity purposes we'll
为了简单起见，我们将使用字符串
just ignore charge at conversion for now
现在暂时忽略转化时的费用
okay great we have our string let's
好的，我们有字符串让我们
complete the body CF with that string
用那根弦完成身体CF
okay at this point everything looks
好的，此时一切看起来
alright we forgot one thing because an
好吧，我们忘记了一件事，因为
unsubscribe we've only requested one
退订我们只要求一个
more call back every time we receive a
每次我们收到更多回电
call back we want to request another one
回电我们想再要求一个
so single step one at a time okay now we
所以现在一次一步就可以了
have our string subscriber let's hook it
让我们的字符串订阅者挂上它
up with HTTP clients so we need a
HTTP客户端，所以我们需要一个
response sorry a response body handler
回应抱歉回应正文处理程序
here response body handler is a
这里响应主体处理程序是
functional interface it takes for a
功能接口
response info returns a subscriber in
响应信息返回订户
our case we'll unconditionally return a
我们的情况下，我们将无条件返回
string subscriber okay so let's run that
字符串订阅者好吧，让我们运行它
okay great so we've response code 200
好的，我们已经回复了代码200
again and we have our response buddy as
再次，我们有我们的反应伙伴
a string let's just take a look at
一个字符串，让我们看看
what's happening here let's add a
这里发生了什么，让我们添加一个
debugging statement to your next call
下次通话的调试语句
oops
哎呀
next it's been called with buffers and
接下来，它被称为缓冲区和
we'll change the URI so that we get some
我们将更改URI，以便获得一些
more response data okay let's run that
更多的响应数据好吧，让我们运行
again okay we can see on Nexus being
再次好吧，我们可以在Nexus上看到
called a number of times
叫过几次
we're T PI buffers that contain the
我们是包含以下内容的T PI缓冲区
response body bytes they all get
它们都获得的响应主体字节
accumulated and then in oncomplete they
积累，然后不完整
get converted to a string and their
转换为字符串及其
string in this case some XML that are
在这种情况下，字符串是一些XML
very a very long line okay so now we've
非常长的线好吧，现在我们已经
seen how to write a custom body
看过如何编写自定义正文
subscriber that converts the response
转换响应的订户
body bytes into a string what if we had
正文字节转换成字符串如果我们有
a flow subscriber to an existing flow
现有流的流订户
subscriber
订户
and we wanted to use that with the HTTP
我们想将其与HTTP一起使用
clients the HTTP client only worked with
客户端HTTP客户端仅与
buddy subscribers so let's see how we
好友订阅者，让我们看看我们如何
can make that work so first of all the
可以做到这一点，所以首先
flow subscriber doesn't have a get buddy
流订户没有好友
method and it also doesn't have a buddy
方法，它也没有伙伴
CF for simplicity let's just print out
CF为简单起见，我们只打印一下
the error if one were to occur I can
如果发生错误，我可以
remove this here so the flow subscriber
在此处删除此流订阅者
still needs some way of exposing its
仍然需要某种方式来暴露它
data so let's give it a private field
数据，所以我们给它一个私有字段
string to hold its body and an accessor
字符串以保持其主体和访问器
get body to return the body ok and
让身体恢复身体正常，
uncomplete now we need to set the body
现在还不完整，我们需要设置身体
field ok so now we are string subscriber
好的，所以现在我们是字符串订阅者
which is an implementation of a flow
这是流程的实现
subscriber how can we use this with a
订户如何将其与
HTTP client well the HTTP client
HTTP客户端很好HTTP客户端
provides convenience static factory
提供便利的静态工厂
methods that adapt between flow
流之间适应的方法
subscriber and body subscriber so let's
订户和正文订户，所以让我们
use one of those
用其中之一
so there's two variants of the from
因此，有两种来自的变体
subscriber adapter the first takes just
用户适配器首先需要
a subscriber and order takes a
订户和订单需要一个
subscriber with a finisher function
具有装订器功能的订户
we're going to use the latter because we
我们将使用后者，因为我们
need to extract the data from the string
需要从字符串中提取数据
subscriber and to complete the HTTP
订户并完成HTTP
computable future with that value so the
具有该价值的可计算的未来，因此
new string subscriber will use the
新的字符串订阅者将使用
string subscriber get body methods to
字符串订阅者获取正文方法
extract the data from the flow
从流中提取数据
subscriber so instead of using a new
订户，所以不要使用新的
string subscriber here we can use the
字符串订阅者，我们可以使用
body subscriber okay let's run that
主体订阅者好吧，让我们运行
again we can see all that on next
再一次，我们可以看到所有的一切
implications and we have the response
暗示，我们有回应
body as a string again we can simplify
主体再次作为字符串我们可以简化
this even further instead of using a
这甚至可以代替使用
body subscriber directly the body
主体订阅者直接将主体
handlers and body handler classes expose
处理程序和主体处理程序类公开
factory methods of similar names so
相似名称的工厂方法
let's use one of those instead
让我们使用其中之一
okay so we don't need to lambda here
好吧，所以我们不需要在这里lambda
anymore should be I use the body handler
我应该使用身体处理程序吗
directly so let's run that to make sure
直接运行，以便确保
it works okay great
很好，很好
same output so we've seen how to write a
相同的输出，所以我们已经看到了如何编写一个
custom body handler and also how to
自定义主体处理程序以及如何
adapt a flow subscriber to the HTTP body
使流订阅者适应HTTP正文
handler or body subscriber there are a
处理程序或正文订阅者
number of adapter methods that support
支持的适配器方法数量
inter operation between regular flow
规则流之间的互操作
types like flow publisher and flow
流发布器和流等类型
subscriber and their HTTP clients
订户及其HTTP客户端
equivalents the one we just seen being
相当于我们刚刚看到的
used in a demo from subscriber has two
订户演示中使用的有两个
variants the first just accepts a flow
第一个只是接受流程
subscriber and returns a body subscriber
订户并返回正文订户
avoid in this case the response body is
在这种情况下，避免响应主体为
not being made available through the
无法通过
HTTP response but instead through some
HTTP响应，但通过一些
other mechanism like an entry in a
其他机制，例如
database the second variant supports a
数据库第二种变体支持
finisher function that will be applied
将应用的装订器功能
after death subscriber has completed and
死亡订户完成后，
we seen an example of this in the demo
我们在演示中看到了一个例子
there are also a similar pair of methods
还有一对类似的方法
from Lion subscriber that interoperate
来自可互操作的Lion用户
with flow subscribers of string where
带有字符串的流订阅者，其中
the response body data is converted to a
响应正文数据转换为
flow of string lines and sent to the
串线流并发送到
flow subscriber line by line this is
流订户流这是
somewhat analogous to bufferedreader
有点类似于bufferedreader
read lines or the nio files Lyons
读取行或niño文件Lyons
method that returns a stream of lines in
返回行流的方法
a file
一份文件
there are also equivalent adapters on
也有等效的适配器
the sending side for request body to
请求正文的发送方
summarize the HTTP client treats boat
总结HTTP客户端对待船
requests and response body as reactive
请求和响应主体为反应性
streams so gets the benefits of
流因此获得的好处
asynchronous programming with
异步编程
non-blocking backpressure we seen how to
无阻塞背压我们看到了如何
write a custom body subscriber
编写自定义正文订阅者
implementation that behaves similar to
行为类似于
the convenience body subscriber returned
便利机构订户返回
by body subscribers off string the HTTP
通过正文订阅者关闭HTTP字符串
client provides a number of adapters
客户端提供了许多适配器
for interoperating with existing
与现有的互操作
reactive streams publishers and
反应流发布商和
subscribers you can download Java 11 now
订阅者，您可以立即下载Java 11
at this URL please join us at open JDK
在此URL上，请在开放的JDK中加入我们
or follow us on Twitter at open JDK or
或通过开放的JDK在Twitter上关注我们，或
hashtag Java 11 my own twitter handle is
我自己的Twitter句柄是Java 11
at checker 999 oracle is the steward of
在检查器999甲骨文是
java providing a large amount of
java提供了大量的
development engineering funding for the
开发工程资金
Java SE platform and open JDK Oracle
Java SE平台和开放的JDK Oracle
provides leading class premier support
提供一流的总理支持
for a low cost that's easy to purchase
易于购买的低成本
with simple pricing tiers thank you for
具有简单的定价等级谢谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]